{
    "subject": "resource/Once_Upon_a_Time_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Jennifer_Morrison",
    "human_readable": "The TV series Once Upon a Time stars Jennifer Morrison.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8173803091049194,
            "question": "Does Jennifer Morrison play a main character in Once Upon a Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7685236930847168,
            "question": "Who stars in the TV series Once Upon a Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7378430366516113,
            "question": "What is the name of the TV series that Jennifer Morrison appears in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6747791767120361,
            "question": "Is Jennifer Morrison an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.673984706401825,
            "question": "Is Jennifer Morrison known for any other roles besides her work in Once Upon a Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4020393490791321,
            "question": "What network broadcasts Once Upon a Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3679044842720032,
            "question": "How many seasons of Once Upon a Time have aired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30618324875831604,
            "question": "What genre is Once Upon a Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18673758208751678,
            "question": "Are there any famous fairy tales featured in Once Upon a Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16772393882274628,
            "question": "Has Once Upon a Time won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The TV series Once Upon a Time stars Jennifer Morrison.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1896_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous fairy tales featured in Once Upon a Time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1896_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Once Upon a Time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1896_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many seasons of Once Upon a Time have aired?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1896_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1896_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Jennifer Morrison played the role of Emma Swan, the main character of the TV series \"Once Upon a Time\". This supports the statement that the TV series Once Upon a Time stars Jennifer Morrison."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Jennifer Morrison's departure from the TV series \"Once Upon a Time\" and her role as Emma Swan. This supports the statement that the TV series \"Once Upon a Time\" stars Jennifer Morrison."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}